A Guide to the Papers of the Nevins-Perkins-Griswold Family of Connecticut, 1731-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Nevins-Perkins-Griswold Family of Connecticut 1731-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7789
This collection consists of ca. 500 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The papers of the Nevins-Perkins-Griswold Family of Connecticut (accession 7789) were deposited for historical reference in the University of Virginia library by Mrs. Rebecca Norris Nevins, c/o Miss Fanny Norris, Venable Lane, Charlottesville, Virginia, on January 5, 1965.
Scope and Content Information
The papers, 1731-1964, of the Nevins-Perkins-Griswold Family of Connecticut consist of ca. 500 items and include correspondence (in part, typescript copies), legal documents, financial records, scrapbooks, photographs, and printed items. As most of the items in the collection consist of personal correspondence between various members of the extended family, or of deeds for sales of land, there is not a great deal of information of general historical interest. (Notable exceptions are the "Civil War" correspondence, 1861-1866, and the letters - in part, copies - of Roger Griswold to his wife.) Primarily, the value of this collection is in the biographical, financial, and legal information which, in summation, provides a substantial history of the extended family throughout the nineteenth century.
Contents List
- Correspondence and Loose Papers
  - R. Wolcott to John Wolcott (with typed copy) 1731 Mar. 25, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Deed, Richard Manwaring to William Manwaring 1737 Apr. 25, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Richard Manwaring to Henry Manwaring 1739 Nov. 9, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Richard Manwaring to Asa Manwaring 1739 Nov. 9, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Asa Manwaring as ececutor of the estate of Richard Manwaring 1755 Mar. 28, 2 p. ADS.
  - Indenture, Asa Manwaring to Robert Manwaring 1773 Nov. 19, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Elijah Waterhouse to Nathaniel Shaw, Jr. 1776 Sept. 11, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, William Moore to Hannah Smith 1778 May 30, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Asa Manwaring to Thomas Miner 1778 Oct. 15, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, John Richard to Nathaniel Shaw 1781 Apr. 26, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, David Manwaring to Nathaniel Shaw 1782 Jan. 5, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Edward Chappell to Thomas Shaw 1782 Dec. 7, 2 p. DS.
  - Lucretia Woodbridge to Mrs. Temperance Shaw 1783 June 25, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Deed, Edward Chappell to Thomas Shaw 1784 May 27, 2 p. DS.
  - Survey of land, James Rogers 1785 May 3, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Simon Gager to Thomas Shaw 1785 June 30, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Elijah Waterhouse to Thomas Shaw 1786 Mar. 7, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Jabez Beebs to Jabes Beebe, Jr. 1786 Aug. 29, 2 p. DS.
  - Civil Judgement, Arnold Wells vs. Jonathan Wells 1787 May 28, 2 p. DS.
  - Bill of Sale, John and Elizabeth Tinker to Thomas Shaw 1791 Apr. 16, 2 p. DS.
  - Bill of Sale, Stephen Maynard and William Hempsted (on behalf of the Town of New London), to Ebenezer Goddard 1792 Feb. 20, 4 p. ADS.
  - [Roger Griswold] to Mrs. Fanny Griswold (with typed copy) 1795 Apr. 28, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Elisha Perkins to Elias Perkins 1796 Feb. 27, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - E[lijah] Perkins to Elias Perkins 1796 Aug. 6, 2 p. ALS.
  - [Roger Griswold] to Fanny [Griswold] w/typed copy 1796 Dec. 5, 4 p. AL (fragment).
  - Bill of Sale, Benjamin Richards to Elias Perkins 1797 Feb. 28, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Elias Perkins, et al 1798 Dec. -, 3 p. ADS.
  - Plat of land, David Manwaring to John Carrol 1800 Jan. -, 2 p. ADS.
  - Plat of land, David Manwaring 1800 Feb. 1, 1 p. ADS.
  - Bill of Sale, Jabez Beebe, Jr., to Elias Perkins 1800 Nov. 19, 2 p. DS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to his wife ca. 1800, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - R[oger] Griswold to Mrs. Fanny Griswold w/typed copy [1801 Jan. 29], 1 p. ALS (fragment). with address leaf
  - Lucretia Law to Elias Perkins 1804 Nov. 19, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia Law to Elias Perkins 1805 Jan. 22, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Indenture, Elias Perkins to Simon Taylor 1805 Mar. 6, 2 p. ADS.
  - B[enjamin] Perkins to Elias Perkins 1806 July 18, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - R.D. Perkins to Elias Perkins 1806 [Aug.] 3 & 20, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Deed, Jonathan and Jonathan Starr, Jr., and Pardon T. Faber to William Beckwith 1807 Feb. 10, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Elizabeth Beckwith to William Beckwith 1807 Feb. 10, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, William Beckwith to Elias Perkins 1807 Feb. 10, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Ezra Morgan to Elias Perkins 1808 June 7, 2 p. DS.
  - Poetry by Lucretia W. Perkins 1814 Feb. 1, 2 p. AMS.
  - Deed, Jabez A. Beebe to Paul Beebe 1815 July 1, 3 p. DS.
  - Agreement to remove barn, Isaac Rogers 1816 June 20, 1 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Henry and Elizabeth Perkins to Elias Perkins 1816 Dec. 26, 4 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Alfred and Lucretia M. Mitchell to Elias Perkins 1818 Feb. 24, 4 p. ADS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Elias Perkins 1818 Apr. 2, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Power of Attorney, William and [Jerusha] Rathbun to Job B. Rathbun 1818 Sept. 30, 4 p. ADS.
  - Deed, William and [Jerusha] Rathbun to Paul Beebe 1818 Oct. 23, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Nathaniel S. Woodbridge to Elias Perkins 1819 Jan. 8, 4 p. ADS.
  - Real Estate Appraisal, Elias Perkins 1819 Jan. 30, 1 p. ADS.
  - Agreement, James Bulkley to Elias Perkins 1819 Jan. 30, 1 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Elias Perkins to Thomas S. Perkins 1819 May 4, 2 p. DS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Mary Ann Griswold 1819 Dec. 11, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Deed, Jabez Manwaring to Thomas S. Perkins 1820 Apr. 24, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Jabez Manwaring to Alfred Mitchell 1820 Apr. 24, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Jabez Manwaring to Elias Perkins 1820 Apr. 24, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, John Howard II to Elias Perkins 1821 Apr. 28, 2 p. DS.
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1825 Dec. 7, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1826 Apr. 6, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to [David H. Nevins] 1826 July 30, 2 p. ALS.
  - Deed, Alfred Mitchell to Elias Perkins 1826 Sept. 19, 2 p. DS.
  - Pass, Ship Carrier John Deshon 1826 Oct. 21, 1 p. DS.
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1826 Dec. 25, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1827 Feb. 20, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to [David Nevins] 1827 Mar. 20, 4 p. AL.
  - Deed, Elias Perkins to Thomas S. Perkins 1827 Oct. 31, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Thomas S. Perkins, et al, to Nathaniel S. Perkins 1827 Oct. 31, 4 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Nathaniel S. Perkins, et al, to Thomas S. Perkins 1827 Oct. 31, 4 p. ADS.
  - Bill of Sale, Nathaniel S. Perkins to Avery Smith and Boswell Smith 1827 Nov. 20, 3 p. ADS.
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1828 Feb. 22, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1828 Mar. 1, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Thomas S. Perkins] to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins 1828 May 9, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Deed, Paul Beebe to Nathaniel S. Perkins 1828 July 19, 2 p. DS.
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1828 Nov. 14, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1829 Jan. 20, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1829 Feb. 14, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1829 Mar. 19, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins [1829] Apr. 4, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1829 Apr. 5, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1829 Apr. 28, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1829 May 8, 1 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins [1829] May 13, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins [1829 May 16], 2 p. AL(fragment). with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1829 July 17, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to [David Nevins] 1829 Aug. 13, 2 p. ALS.
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to [David Nevins] 1829 Sept. 22, 2 p. ALS.
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David Henry Nevins 1829 Nov. 14, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1830 Jan. 17, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1830 Jan. 26, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins [1830] May 1, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1830 June 10, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1830 July 12, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1830 Nov. 3, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1831 Jan. 10, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1831 Mar. 11, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1831 Mar. 26, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1831 June 21, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1831 Aug. 20, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1831 Sept. 10, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins with AL from [his mother] 1831 Nov. 14, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1831 Dec. 21, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Jan. 18, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Feb. 21, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Mar. 14, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1832 May 9, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1832 May 14, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 May 18, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 May 28, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 July 30, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Aug. 24, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Aug. 27, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to D. H. Nevins 1832 Sept. 21, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1832 Oct. 12, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1832 Oct. 19, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Nov. 12, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Nov. 23, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to D. H. Nevins 1832 Nov. [?], 1 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1832 Dec. 9, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1832 Dec. 17, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Jan. 2, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Jan. 11, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [David Nevins] to [Lucretia Nevins] 1833 Jan. 15, 3 p. AL (copy).
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Jan. 23, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Jan. 27, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Feb. 4, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to Lucretia M. Nevins 1833 Feb. 8, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Feb. 9, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Feb. 17, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. N[evins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Mar. 4, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Mar. 8, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Mar. 19, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Mar. 27, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1833 Mar. 28, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Apr. 1, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] and [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Apr. 4, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Apr. 11, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins and [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Apr. 22, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Apr. 25, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 May 9, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 May 16, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 May 31, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. N[evins] to David H. Nevins 1833 June 22, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 July 11, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 July 22, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 July 27, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 July [?], 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Aug. 8, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Miguel Cabrera de Navares to David H. Nevins 1833 [Aug.] 30, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Sept. 20, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to David H. Nevins 1833 Sept. 26, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Deed, James Rogers to Thomas S. Perkins 1833 Sept. 26, 1 p. DS.
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Sept. 28, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Ray Palmer to David H. Nevins 1833 Nov. 6, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Nov. 9, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1833 Nov. 30, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
    w/recept, Ray Palmer
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Dec. 17, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Mr. and Mrs. [Henry] Nevins to Lucretia M. Nevins 1833 Dec. 30, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Jan. 11, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Mr. and Mrs. [Henry] Nevins to Lucretia M. Nevins 1834 Jan. 14, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. N[evins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Jan. 25, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - "Mother" to Lucretia M. Nevins 1834 Feb. 5, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Feb. 11, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Feb. 25, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Mar. 17, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Apr. 4, 1 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 May 5, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - L[ucretia] M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1834 May 8, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 May 24, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 June 5, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 June 21, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1834 June 23, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 June 29, 4 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Mr. & Mrs. [Henry] Nevins to Lucretia M. Nevins 1834 July 7, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins 1834 July 15, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to Henry Nevins 1834 July 17, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Sept. 3, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] and [?] to David H. Nevins 1834 Oct. 9, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Oct. 13, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Oct. 23, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Oct. [?], 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins and "aunt" 1834 Nov. 3, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Nov. 12, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Nov. 20, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - L[ucretia] and [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1834 Nov. 24, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Nov. [?], 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to [David Nevins] 1834 Dec. 1, 2 p. ALS.
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Dec. 4, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Dec. 14 [-15], 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1834 Dec. 22, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1834 Dec. 31, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Jan. 4, 3 p. ALS (fragment). with address leaf
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Jan. 16, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Jan. 23[-24], 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Jan. 28, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Feb. [?], 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia and [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1835 Mar. 6, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1833 Mar. 13, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - L[ucretia] and [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1835 Mar. 16, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Mar. 27, 1 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 May 16, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 June 1, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 July 10, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1835 Aug. 7, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Sept. 9, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. Nevins to David H. Nevins 1835 Sept. 20, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1835 Sept. 21, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1835 Dec. 29, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry] Nevins to David H. Nevins 1836 Jan. 4, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1836 Apr. 30, 4 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1836 June 10, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lease, Thomas S. Perkins 1836 Sept. 22, 4 p. ADS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins [1836], 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Land Grant, to Daniel Low and Charles F. Moulton 1837 Apr. 15, 1 p. DS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins 1837 Aug. 4, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Deed, John N. Watrons to Thomas S. Perkins 1837 Aug. 15, 1 p. DS.
  - Land Grant, to Daniel Low and Charles F. Moulton 1838 July 28, 1 p. DS.
  - Henry Gardner, Jr., to Thomas S. Perkins 1840 June 6, 1 p. ANS.
  - J. R. Finn to Thomas S. Perkins 1841 June 4, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Melanethon [Stan] to David H. Nevins 1841 July 23, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Receipt, Thomas S. Perkins 1841 Nov. 13, 2 p. ANS.
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins 1841 Dec. [11], 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Thomas S. Perkins to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins 1842 July 2, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Melanethon [Stan] to David H. Nevins 1842 Aug. [4], 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - D. Manwaring to David H. Nevins [1842] Oct. 13, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1842 Oct. 31, 3 p. AL(fragment). with address leaf
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1843 May 18, 4 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to D. H. Nevins 1843 May 27, 4 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1843 June 19, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Nevins] to D. H. Nevins 1843 July 20, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Nevins] to D. H. Nevins 1843 Aug. 17, 3 p. AL(fragment). with address leaf
  - Power of Attorney, Thomas S. Perkins to Mary An Perkins; Mary An Perkins to Elias Perkins, II 1843 Sept. 27 and 1844 Jan. 24, 3 p. ADS.
  - L[ucretia Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1844 Feb. 4, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia M. [Stan] to David H. Nevins 1844 May 6, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Lucretia Stan] to Henry Nevins 1844 Nov. 9, 4 p. AL. with address leaf
  - [Henry Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1844 Dec. 26, 3 p. AL. with address leaf
  - F. M. Caulkins to D. H. Nevins 1845 Jan. 12, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Mary [S.] Thomas to Cornelia L. Perkins 1845 Feb. 10, 1 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry Barnard] to Mrs. Thomas S. Perkins 1845 Apr. 1, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1845 Apr. 3, 2 p. AL. with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Stan] to David H. Nevins 1845 May 18, 3 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Stan] to David H. Nevins 1845 June 29, 4 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1846 Feb. 6, 3 p. AL, with address leaf
  - [Henry Nevins] to David H. Nevins 1846 Mar. 26, 3 p. AL, with address leaf
  - John H. [Gourhe] to D. H. Nevins 1847 May 15, 4 p. ALS(fragment). with address leaf
  - Contract, David H. Nevins and Cornelia L. Perkins 1845 May 25, 1 p. ADS(fragment).
  - Deed, Henry and M. A. Perkins 1847 Sept. 21, 1 p. ADS.
  - F. M. C[aulkins] to D. H. Nevins 1847 Oct. 20, 4 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - [Henry Nevins] to D. H. Nevins 1848 Nov. 1, 1 p. AL, with address leaf
  - M[elanethon] Stan to David H. Nevins 1850 May 3, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Lucretia [Stan] to David H. Nevins 1850 Sept. 5, 2 p. ALS, with address leaf
  - Cornelia [Nevins] to her sister 1851 Mar. 18, 4 p. ALS.
  - [Henry Nevins] to [David Nevins] 1851 Nov. 19, 4 p. AL.
  - Deed, Ichabod Clark to Peter Darrow 1852 May 6, 2 p. DS.
  - [Title Search] 1852 May 6, 2 p. AD.
  - Deed, Frederick, W. Perkins to David H. Perkins 1852 Dec. 6, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Jacob A. and Mary G. P. Camp to David H. Nevins 1852 Dec. 24, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Roger G. Perkins to David H. Nevins 1853 Apr. 11, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, David H. Nevins, et al, to Mary E. Holt 1856 Sept. 11, 1 p. DS.
  - Receipt, David H. Perkins 1857 Apr. 17, 1 p. ANS.
  - Deed, David H. and Cornelia L. Nevins to Town of Waterford 1857 Aug. 1, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Eliza Solomon to Sarah Darrow 1858 Dec. 24, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Estate of Nathaniel S. Perkins, Jr., to David H. Nevins 1859 Jan. 4, 3 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Joseph Perkins to David H. Perkins 1859 May 30, 3 p. DS.
  - Power of Attorney, Maurice Perkins to Mary A. Perkins 1860 Feb. 17, 4 p. ADS.
  - Receipt 1860 [Nov.] 20, 1 p. ANS.
  - Deed, Estate of Nathaniel S. Perkins, Jr., to Mary Ann. Nevins 1860 Dec. 17, 2 p. ADS.
  - Deed, Joseph Perkins and Roger G. Perkins to Mary A. Perkins [1860 Dec. 27], 2 p. DS(fragment).
  - Deed, Jacob A. Camp (guardian) to Mary A. Perkins 1861 Feb. 12, 2 p. DS.
  - Cornelia [Nevins] to Joseph [Perkins] 1861 Apr. 23, 3 p. ALS.
  - David H. and Cornelia Nevins to Mary Ann Perkins 1861 July 23, 2 p. DS.
  - Joseph Perkins to his mother [1862 Sept. 10], 2 p. ALS.
  - [Joseph Perkins] to his mother [1862 Sept. 20], 2 p. AL(fragment).
  - Deed, Josiah Crocker to David H. Nevins 1863 Feb. 20, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Mary A. Perkins to Cornelia L. Nevins 1863 Aug. 29, 2 p. DS.
  - Deed, Mary Ann Perkins, et al, to David H. Nevins 1863 Aug. 29, 4 p. ADS.
  - Subscriptions to support war [ante 1863 Nov. 25], 3 p. 3 items.
  - Deed, Cornelia L. and David H. Perkins to Mary Ann Perkins, with undated copy 1863 Nov. 28, 1 p. 1 p. DS(fragment).
  - Enlistment roster 1864 Mar. 18, 1 p. DS.
  - Subscription list 1864 Apr. 25, 1 p. AD.
  - Eliza E. and Charles W. Croker to David H. Nevins 1865 Apr. 18, 2 p. DS.
  - [?] to a cousin 1865 June 16, 4 p. AL(fragment).
  - C[ornelia Nevins] to her parents [ca. 1861-1865], 10 p. ALS(fragment).